<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Chatter</title>
    <link>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Chatter</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://thechatter.netlify.app/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://thechatter.netlify.app/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 15:49:43 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Twitters Downfall</title>
      <link>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/twitters-downfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 15:49:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/twitters-downfall/</guid>
      <description>Twitter is the worlds largest micro-blogging app, rivaled only by Koo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diary of a Wimpy Kid Diper Överlode Book Review</title>
      <link>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/diary-of-a-wimpy-kid-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 19:50:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/diary-of-a-wimpy-kid-book-review/</guid>
      <description>Im sure all of you can guess by the title, that there&amp;rsquo;s alot of potty humor in this. I mean, Loded Diper has been an iconic name for as long as I can remember Diper Överlode was an unexpected but welcome addition to the Diary of a Wimpy Kid series, although not containing much, it was an enjoyable read for me and all my classmates.
Spoiler alert! (but you knew that) Educational Value B- Doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain much, but teaches readers the value of music, and how much artists strive for the spotlight, however small that spotlight is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s It Like Owning a Dog</title>
      <link>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/whats-it-like-owning-a-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 19:44:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/whats-it-like-owning-a-dog/</guid>
      <description>Prologue So I&amp;rsquo;m sure you all have debated about having a dog, whether it be as a companion, guard-dog, or a emotional support pet (in my case, yes). But then you realise how much of a pain in the backside it can be, all the way from potty training, to even simple manners&amp;hellip; In that case, this blog is for you.
The upsides We all know how cute dogs are, and even a street dog can smile its way out of a jam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Made This Blog</title>
      <link>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/why-i-made-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:20:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thechatter.netlify.app/post/why-i-made-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding to be able to move readers with your writing. That’s why I decided to create a blog. To Inspire My audience1 Writing a blog allows one to express ones feelings and air out ones judgements about life, It could also affect the readers life by allowing them to:
Improve their quality of life. Increase their day&amp;rsquo;s output. Make something lovely. Lend a hand to others. All of this is possible thanks to the power of a blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
